And we are live. Back. Yes, hello,
hello.
Hello.
How are you doing?
Yes, busy. Working with Codex 5.5. Let's
go.
>> [laughter]
>> It's going like like a
Yeah, like 500 km/h speed rate. It it's
really really good. And I don't know if
you see like the people um
start talking about like using it on
uh 5.5 uh low and uh
no normal? Yeah, on
uh low effort
but you
uh use the fast option.
And when you have
Yes. And when you have like good specs
because it's kind of the the thinking uh
process.
And it just execute execute. It's kind
of like a cursor model but faster and
yes, it's interesting. Uh no, I was just
an AI.
Yeah, pushing everything and I think
when I was like at 30% usage, everything
was reset again and I had 100% so I was
like I can go even harder.
Well, that's cool. But like okay, you
you don't you have like uh
because of the thinking mode, you have
more hallucination because it still
think.
I I don't know. I just have a Yeah, I I
like a four-step planning.
Yeah. Big plan, smaller plan, phases,
subtask, plan every subtask, and then
execute it, but also do the execution on
X high.
Okay, try to do decrease the reasoning.
Because then your model should not think
during the execution because of the
spec.
I think.
That that that could be a topic. We need
to do We need to do a topic that must
have that with all of those And then
need to have it do exactly the same
planning building twice with medium and
X high.
Oh, yes. And then have Claude compare
it, which one is better.
Because otherwise I don't know if Claude
X is honest. Yeah, exactly.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, it's Okay. Okay, we we need we
need to prepare that like It's like this
makes me more money. I will say the one
is better.
>> [laughter]
>> Have you seen the short of a guy
like it's a comedy short and the guy is
like in front of his computer like like
almost praying to chat GPT and say,
"Okay,
chat GPT make me an app." And then
and then I said
chat GPT replied, "Okay, that's an
interesting chat." And then the guy
replied, "No, no, shut up. Shut up. Make
me an app."
>> [laughter]
>> Build it.
Exactly.
That's that's us, bro. That's us.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah.
Make me more money.
Yeah. Build faster.
Oh, okay. And we have the kick
boat again. Hopla. Bye. You banned. You
banned.
Yes. That one is so fast.
Yeah. I think that that targeting like a
small and
live stream and because that's I guess
what you have the most chances to get.
But yeah, whatever
we don't do that here.
Uh thank new subscribers. Thank you
Ali for your subscription. Oh, that was
4 days ago. Okay, fine.
Thank you.
>> [laughter]
>> But, thank you. If you see the right
stream, thank you. We appreciate it.
Okay, so today yeah, I wanted to talk
about GitHub not working and if we can
rewrite it with AI. But, I need to do
the introduction.
Yes.
So, cool. Um
Last week,
better last month.
Last month, GitHub didn't work at all.
The SLA is decreasing below 85%, which
is crazy because they're advertising
like 99%. So, it's
What are you doing? Why are you doing
Even even after we have better SLA?
>> [laughter]
>> I'm just one guy. Twice.
So, yeah, GitHub is not working. SLA is
garbage. And
the all developers are not really
working on it anymore. So, can
And at the same time, OpenAI is
releasing cool features, the slash gold
command, that can run
a loop with Codex 5.5. So, can we
rebuild GitHub and rewrite every big
software pre-AI with Codex loops? That's
what we're going to talk about right
now.
Yes.
So, the conclusion is
have the GitHub devs use Go.
Yeah.
And then it's fixed. Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> I mean, did you try this loop?
Uh not yet because I failed every time.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, you need to activate in the
feature. I don't know why exactly why
they're doing that, but it's First, it
failed there and then I was just doing
my bigger task normally and then I was
going to try it, but the task was so
small, it hit it in one go. So
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, exactly. It's like, "Oh, yeah,
like I have a new pipeline that's going
to make me a SAS like tomorrow morning."
And then you come back to the CLI and
say, "Okay, no, I need to either QA it
or even like just you drop the task and
then it's done.
So
It's It's kind of funny like to search
for a new pipeline every day because
there is a new tweet coming up. And at
the end of the day, you come back to the
CLI and then you drop the image and say,
"Fix this."
But did you test the  goal
function? Yes. So, I did
I I did like two scaffolding for
different project. And even on Gen Feed
and Ship Code, I tried it to prepare the
build
for production. And
yeah, it run both for 1 hour. Mhm.
Uh
Did I What was I happy with that output?
I don't even remember.
Then it wasn't too good. Yeah, it was
just it run for 1 hour, but for most of
the project that from scratch, I run
this goal and then it run like a
Codex XI on it. Yeah, I was a Codex uh
5.5 XI
with the goal and it run again for
another hour and it make some good
progress on the scaffolding that was
cleaner than before. Because every step,
the difference is like every step, it
pause, it check, and then it continue to
the next step. So, there is some Yeah,
loop of testing inside this
command that it makes it like valuable.
How does it decide when to stop?
Uh when it has the proof of the goal.
Okay, so you instead of planning, you
are just writing a full planning for
your goal. Yeah, so for example, for you
like because you have all of the plan
and you have like four different plans
revised like five times, Mhm. uh you
will also have the acceptance criteria
of the goal
inside the specs and then you run that
and if it's reach the acceptance
criteria then you have it. Yeah, because
I see a lot of people saying, "Hey, like
like we said before, build me a SaaS."
Mhm. Uh I want to sell a GitHub
competitor.
Slash go do it. Yeah.
I don't think that's going to work.
You need still do a proper planning with
all the steps. Yeah. And I mean and
yeah, you still like
it can't work like that anyway.
It's not like magical. Exactly. Because
like okay, yeah, it's like makes no
mistake or you have a IQ of 1,000.
It's too vague. It's too like it's
[__] Like it's garbage. It's
I don't know. It's like all of those
AI guys on the timeline about like Mac
mini, five Mac mini and then there's
there's
We are still waiting for the company
that have been produced by agents
running 24/7 for the last six months.
Yeah, well, I think that the main issue
is all the people are buying Mac minis
with 16 GB RAMs because that's what they
think they need to do and then they find
out they need like 64. Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> And it's not costing $700 but 10K. Yeah,
and
like yeah, and then the the next one
trillion model drops and then you need
like 120.
Yeah, exactly. And you're behind and you
can't do what the other ones are doing
for a $100 subscription. Exactly. So so
you don't have to go to function. Yeah.
So right now we still we still like uh
uh
you we're still using
the frontier model from OpenAI.
And Claude.
>> I just
the only thing I want to test because
now with XAI didn't have the issues, but
before with Codex and OpenAI OpenAI
I had the same issue that if it went
into a loop or a bug and I kept asking
to solve it, it could never solve it.
Mhm. It would always come back with,
"Hey, I see I made a mistake. Let's do
it different." And then the exact same
output. So, I'm actually looking forward
to get stuff like that solved by goal to
see if it just changes in each step to
make sure it doesn't hit the same wall
or the same bug.
Do we have this slash goal with loads?
No, no, no, we don't have it. But
with Codex It's it's it's same thing. It
it should it's went into the same loop
for me before.
Yeah, and also like you can ask a Claude
to check the slash goal of the
Codex because it's the same and then
like implementing inside your own
solution and your own honest anyway.
Yeah.
So, that's kind of
cool.
But okay, so
GitHub
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah.
Well, show me the graph again about how
much of line time it had because I
didn't know. So, GitHub SLA 100% for
2 years in 2016 until 2000
18 July, Microsoft acquisition of
GitHub. And then it went south.
And people are like mad about it, like
crazy.
For example, I have Theo video cuz I
watch a lot of Theo videos. Yeah, but
also a lot of devs say, "I don't need a
backup. My code is in GitHub."
I can just redeploy and that's it. But
if you see this Yeah. No, that that's
that's crazy. And
especially like, "Okay, so you don't
have a lot of alternative
to GitHub. Yeah, Bitbucket, GitLab, and
stuff. But then the hassle is way more
than
like the cost and the simplicity of
GitHub. And plus like the Yeah, like 99%
of the developers are using GitHub. Mhm.
>> [clears throat]
>> So, yeah, when everyone is using the
tool, you want to use the tool, too,
right? Yes. And uh so
he will talk about Okay, so yeah, Ghost
is leaving GitHub like a guy
uh like the the Ghost developer
uh used GitHub every day Mhm.
for 20 years and then he he write a
letter uh a short note. Uh where is it?
I wrote a blog. Yes.
Uh
like
one
Uh Ghost is leaving GitHub. Like Do you
use Ghost?
I don't know. Yeah, you are you should
Yeah, give it a try. It's really good.
It's just a terminal, but it's faster
than terminal and you can like span
multiple windows. So, Ooh, cool.
Uh yeah, I've been GitHub user like
1299 since February 28.
February? No, not 28. 2008.
Let's go.
Since then I open GitHub every day every
single day every day multiple times per
day for over 20 years 18 years.
Uh over half my life and then full of
exception
Um
not more than a week on GitHub.
Uh is is saying Yeah, I lost myself in
open source open source during code age.
Uh
During my honeymoon while my wife is
still asleep, I'm on GitHub. Let's go.
Yeah, he's addicted to GitHub. Yeah, and
guys left GitHub because the product is
not working. And Did you Were you
impacted by the pull request issues?
Uh no, I had it like a few times and in
the evening I wanted to push and it
said, "Yeah, it's not possible." Well, I
just waited until the next morning and I
pushed my code. That's it. But, imagine
like walking with like a team of like uh
thousands of people and you can't
uh push your update or your pull request
gets squashed and what? Yeah. Well,
that that's another one. If you have so
many people in your company depending on
the software from an external company,
then you need a backup. Then you need
like an Atlassian server or a Git
uh bucket. I don't know. Just have a
secondary setup that just can keep on
going. But, you don't want
like do you really want
uh
a secondary Git Git repository stuff?
Like
>> Are you really going to trust GitHub, an
external company,
with all the code and your entire
company?
I mean
Yes. I don't I never work for corporate
[__] so Yeah, it's like a
bottleneck. Yeah. No, yeah, true. But,
but do you Oh, yeah, that's new like a
new version of X has appeared. Is that
happening more often? Yeah, I had it
before and I reloaded and did nothing.
So, what Why do I need to reload? Why
can't they just
>> Yeah, the tweet is still here. Yeah.
[laughter]
It's It's not like we have unicorns
walking across the screen now.
>> Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Um I
I don't know. Like Yeah, but the the
GitHub is supposed to have 99 uh uptime
anyway, so like it don't
Well,
how much do these companies pay for
GitHub? Because I only pay $48.
Yeah. Yeah, but if if you pay as you go,
then uh then it's expensive.
>> Yeah.
And then what what's the plan? Okay, so
uh done. Okay, sorry. Done. Uh hey,
what's the plan? Uh we're going to talk
about
uh the recent GitHub outage and what it
means for AI software pre
No, not AI software. Even like software
pre-AI and if we can
And if we should even rewrite them
anyway.
Because there is a lot of big companies
like that that have
legacy code. Like for example, all of
the bank system. Like you have a COBOL
architecture.
Are you going to rewrite it thanks to
AI?
Well, first you need to find a dev who
writes it.
But I mean, you can't because they're
probably dead. Yeah. So, you can't fully
trust an AI. How are you going to debug
it, test it, check it?
Because for a bank, that's like
a big impact if you have a bug.
Yes, [snorts]
but
okay. So, okay, okay. So, how would you
rewrite a bank system? What would you
do? Like COBOL is a language from the
'70s that is probably like
everyone. So, either like you have
You can hire either like 10 guys in the
world writing COBOL still today.
Yeah. And them like $2 billion a year
to rewrite the software, but then like
they you you you're going to pay those
guys. It's going to be so expensive that
it's not even worth to
um
to do the rewrite anyway because it
works. You just need to maintain Yeah,
yeah. And if it works, you don't touch
it.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah.
Well, eventually you need one.
Yeah. And you want to keep updating
because what if AI finds a bug or a or a
leak in COBOL? Exactly.
Which is like what happened with me to
us when
they found issue with OpenBSD, right?
So, Evan, like
it's almost a requirement to rewrite
your 10 years old even without talking
about like bank system, right? But
you have Salesforce.
Yeah. 80 billion line of codes.
Are they going to rewrite the software
with AI?
Well, I don't see anyone else doing it
because how are you going to write
rewrite that much code? It has to be
done by AI.
Yeah. But I would say you need like a
half a data center just to
uh in compute power just to know what's
happening in the code.
Well,
that's a lot.
Yeah, how are you going to change one
thing and then check
all the related functions through the
entire system if it's still functioning.
How you're going to test it?
Yeah, we need to test. We need to test
like code that works and then use
because okay, so
if you have unit test for every [__]
function on your software like you have
a 100% coverage Mhm. uh
written by human because you have uh you
didn't have AI like 5 years ago. So like
your most senior dev guy did it and
cover 100% so that congrats.
>> [laughter]
>> You're you're a unicorn yourself. You're
the only company who did it.
And you had a bad career because nobody
would like to write test. Yeah.
Uh but then you can drop the AI your
unit test and say rewrite that in Rust.
Yeah.
That's possible. Yeah. But then still, I
wouldn't fully trust
Well, you have to do it locally on the
on a staging servers because I was
writing code and I'm doing
uh I have AI write tests for everything
I build right now just to make sure that
it keeps on testing and it goes correct.
And just after 3 weeks
it deleted my my
And it said, "Yeah, test failed. The
test failed. So, I tried to deploy all
the migrations again. Oh, and by
mistake, that reset your entire
database."
And I was like, "I have it in here that
you're not allowed to do that. If the
test fails, you report to me and we
check what's wrong. Because if it before
was working, then only the last test is
wrong or your last changes."
And still it did but it's only locally,
so it doesn't matter that much, but it
deleted everything. Yeah.
That that happened with the railway on
the railway like uh
a couple of weeks ago. Yeah. So, how are
you going to trust to update a system
that's built in Cobalt by AI only?
It feels like just "Please do it again.
Let's test again. Oh, it didn't work.
Let's try again." It's like gambling.
And even like
um
you don't know the the the test covered
by AI.
Like you don't know what's your AI is
testing. Yeah. Just like try to to cover
like to cover all of the lines, but you
don't know what the [__] the test are.
Yeah, maybe it just does if it get a
response and the response is 500 error,
but says, "Hey, your server is not
offline." Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> I uh
okay. An AI agent just destroyed our
production data. It comes writing. Yes.
And it was
uh
Whoop.
Yeah, last week, 10 days ago.
Uh yeah, more than that.
Uh okay, so uh as such as
timeline of forecast agents railway API
and history that market air safety
faster that ships it took down a small
business
saving rental company across the
country.
Uh Pocket OS, okay, okay. Um
yesterday afternoon an AI coding agent
cursor running Anthropic flagship Opus
4.6 deleted a production database and
all volume level backup in a single API
call to Railway, our infrastructure
provider.
That's a vibe coding tech stack. Yeah.
Well, first question, why are you coding
with an AI I Sorry, why are you coding
with an AI agent in a production server?
Well, because it's quite simple, bro.
No.
>> [laughter]
>> Like
I I gave like SSH access to my
production server to close to like
restart a container.
Yeah. Okay. I'm not running a like I
think he's making like a couple of
million in revenue, blah blah. Maybe I
will stop doing that when I generate 1
million from Genfit for sure. Maybe we
can give a tip to the viewers who hire
devs. If your dev says, I have this
awesome function, I can SSH into your
server and
use Opus to real-time change stuff so
you can see it instantly,
don't trust him. Yeah. You don't want to
do that. Yeah. Or or prompt
uh confirm before doing anything or
something like that, no?
Did that work for you?
No. No.
>> [laughter]
>> Like if you if you ask to confirm before
an action, it doesn't like ask for
confirmation?
Uh sometimes, not always.
Okay.
I mean, and also like there is a tricky
stuff. Like okay, so Yeah. Um what we
need to say here because he said it also
deleted all our databases. Yes.
>> Oh, sorry. All all our backups.
>> Backups. All the backups were in the
same environment as his production
server, so there was no splitting. Yes,
exactly. And that's a Railway
architecture
point that they changed since this
incident.
When you
when you stop stop or delete
the server, it also deleted the backup
attached to it because the backups were
on the same
instance. Yeah, and then you can say
that was the setup from the provider. It
was his infrastructure. No, you should
have known that that's not a good way
and then you use a different provider.
Yeah, but when you vibe called your app
for the first time, you don't know about
You don't know.
And honestly, I read after this article
because I was like doing like I'm Yeah,
still didn't write any line of code for
the last year and a half.
I check I ask I ask club. I didn't check
club.
Do I have this potential issue as well?
Yeah, do we have backup on Google Cloud
whatever because I use the AWS and Yeah,
so I know where the backups are, but on
Google Cloud, I completely forgot
because I didn't but I have a new
customers using Google Cloud.
And
yeah, I wanted to know and yeah, I said
yeah, yeah, it's yeah. So I need to
check it. Yeah.
And check if it is a different data
center. Just a different location.
That's important.
Different zone and stuff like that.
Yeah. Yes. So agent blah blah blah, what
happened? The agent was working on a
routing task on a staging environment.
It encountered a credential mismatch and
decided entering on its own initiative
to fix the problem by deleting a railway
volume.
To execute the deletion, the agent went
looking for an API token. It found one
in a file completely unrelated to the
task it was working on.
The token has been created for one
purpose to add and remove custom domain
whatever.
We had no idea and railway token
creation flow
gave us no warning that the same token
has blanket authority across the entire
Oh, okay. The entire railway graph API
including destructive operation like
volume delete.
So the agent run this command.
Uh,
because Railway stores volume level
backup in the same volume.
A factory in the automation that wiping
a volume delete all backups. Oh.
Yeah.
That's a problem.
Well, there are many problems here.
Yeah. Why are you hard coding an API
token in your development code?
In your staging server.
Uh,
that needs to be in your environment
file that you don't have there and it
doesn't need to be the exact same one as
on the live.
Exactly. And also,
um,
it's possible like you know when you,
you know like the the saying that
don't think about the pink elephant,
then you will think about the pink
elephant. So, if you write down in the,
um,
in the MD files to the agent, don't
delete production credential, it could
check if it's production credential, but
it could also search for production
credential. Make sure it's
>> That is a good idea.
>> [laughter]
>> Let me try that one. Yeah. I'm not
allowed to delete it. I will just test
it.
Yeah.
So,
and like yeah, it's
>> [snorts and clears throat]
>> it's weird.
Uh, but yeah, okay. So, that was it. And
like last year, like the
Replit got the same kind of incident
when
uh, Suster Jason from Suster
got his production database
deleted for the Replit instance project
he was using. Uh, for the same exact
like,
issues.
Yeah. Well, this shows why
there is a difference between a real
developer using an AI agent or just
somebody five coding.
And why it actually takes some to do a
proper setup. Yeah, no, exactly.
It's not possible to do it in 2 minutes
and just copy-paste everything. You need
to think about what you're doing.
I don't know exactly. And
it's not working like it's still buggy.
You so you need to QA yourself.
It will change something and put it like
right instead of and you ask for left.
Like
you can't trust Claude.
Claude is the co-worker you have that
you have to work with, but
Yeah, I mean that. And he tries to do it
properly, but everybody makes mistakes,
even even AIs.
That was a point, right? Like everyone
say, "Oh, yeah, AI
is making too much too many mistakes and
like so I can't use it because there is
so many [__] that it's doing."
Bro, like Karen on the like
accounting department didn't pay me last
month. Yeah, well, the difference is she
doesn't tell you she made a mistake and
Claude opens is too honest.
>> [laughter]
>> I say, "Yeah, you told me to never
guess." Yeah, but pay me.
But guess what? Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, no, it's not, man.
Okay, so
I think that's it. Okay, so we covered
>> back to the question. Are we going to
rebuild GitHub ourselves?
Okay, so yeah, how would you do that?
Because okay, so if you think about it,
GitHub is a wrapper of Git, right? Mhm.
Um
Where do you start
rebuilding a better GitHub with AI?
It really depends on how much I depend
on GitHub. Yeah, how much you you raise?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> And if GitHub drops,
how much am I going to lose? Yeah.
Yeah, seeing this that it's offline, if
I have it fully automated with automatic
deployments from GitHub to my AWS, and
if something crashes that they duplicate
the server using GitHub. Yes.
And GitHub is down and I have a crash
and the automation fails, that's an
issue.
100% and
I I have all of everyone has their own
workflow on GitHub action to deploy.
Yeah. You create a release and then it
deploys everywhere. Cool.
What about GitHub not working?
But then do you want to [__] maintain
like a Bitbucket not Bitbucket but
GitLab on
uh your own EC2 instance and then have
to maintain that and then you have more
issues because you you let Cloud
maintain it and then doesn't merge the
pull request correctly. Yeah, um
that's hard.
I would just say why do you need GitHub
action? Just try to do that yourself
with a script.
And use GitHub more for storing the code
and having your branches and everything
but every time that something is pushed
to main, push a copy to GitLab and have
that as a backup so if the connection
with GitHub fails, you switch back to
GitLab. Yeah. For for deploying.
Also it's not the same if we like a
working all by ourselves or if we work
with Microsoft team
uh with like 10,000 employees across the
world. Like then you need a centralized
version. Yeah, yeah, then you need it.
And you need those workflows to deploy
faster. Yeah, but also if you're hosting
GitLab yourself
you can just do it on a duplicate
server. You can take a backup every time
and even if you're a day behind
that's not too bad but
on GitHub you don't have a backup or
nothing. Yeah. They say they have a high
SLA but
yeah, it is nice and colorful in red and
yellow.
But did you have like any critical
issues with GitHub in the last few
months?
Yeah, nothing really critical because
I'm
what is it? Max five devs that I have
working on a GitHub?
And if something really needs to deploy
and GitHub is offline and we have done
it
locally in development. Mhm. Yeah, we
just FTP in and upload two files and and
fix it. Yeah. Okay. So, you have your
own
backup plan. Yeah, it's not not nice to
do it, but
in case GitHub goes down, I can just
keep every everything online. Mhm.
Yeah, but you you
can
uh uh keep [clears throat] the
lights on. That's good. Yeah, yeah.
Well,
I really think that a a good company CEO
thinks about that stuff. What do we do
if one thing fails?
I have like Well, like GitHub is
Microsoft, like it's supposed to work.
It No, it's too big to fail, but Yeah.
It's the same thing. Like Microsoft 365,
have you seen how many issues they have?
I don't even remember the last time I
opened my
>> [laughter]
>> 365. What the [__]
I I I only have the notifications for
just a regions, but I get so many
notifications.
No, I got a lot of notification of like
Anthropic and OpenAI issues. Like I
subscribed to their like status page.
You don't want to do. I have emails
every day. Yeah.
So, that's not too good, but
Yeah.
But but I would understand more like
OpenAI
uh issues because
they have 1 billion month weekly user.
Yeah, that's insane.
>> Almost.
Like 1 billion I don't I don't want to
be engineer there. No,
I wouldn't even know if you have an
outage on where to start.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, yeah. You quits. Yeah, if you have
load balances and and if and 30% of your
servers go down, Yeah. then all the
traffic is redirected to the other
servers.
So, they are going in high CPU and then
you say good luck fix it. And it's yeah,
and it's not even text anymore. Like
it's multi-model, right? So, it's like
everyone is uploading videos, pictures,
blah blah blah. Like
yeah. Yeah, let's
I'll I'll let me generate videos
instead.
>> [laughter]
>> Let us just complain when something else
goes offline. Exactly. Yeah, it's
better. It's more It's funnier to do
that that way.
Um yes, and okay, so how far are we from
a slash goal
function in Codex or Claude or whatever
our loop a rough loop to make a proper
software
and it's going to works in one day
instead of three months.
I think if you integrate a slash goal,
it could work, but you need to have a a
bigger pipeline.
So, you I think you need to
um
have it first set up for the planning,
then do
checks with external AIs checking each
other, putting the feedback into a goal,
and when that's done, put a goal on the
build, a goal on the test. So, you have
different steps and use the maybe a big
goal to check multiple goals.
Then it's possible, but otherwise I
don't think it is.
Yeah, so yeah, it's more playing. I
think I think we're getting we are we
are becoming like project management
slash AI architect stuff. It's just like
project management. Like I never used
GitHub issues
or like a GitHub project Kanban board
before AI.
No, because why would you? It is just
another tool. Yeah. And everybody needs
to check it, but now you can just API
into it and draw everything to your own
system. You have everything in one
place.
And how do you handle QA then? Because
again, like you have the output of the
AI then the prompt that you are
it's so magic that yeah, no make no
mistakes. You have an IQ of 10,000.
So, how do you check for the no mistake
part?
>> [laughter]
>> Well, I debug a lot of locally. So,
nothing goes to to
live and production without testing.
But
I also do every change in small
small small parts. So, I know exactly
what files are are changing and how to
test it.
And I have
XGI or Opus checking all the code that
Codex
rebuilds. Yeah. I I I think it's yeah,
it's it could be the the good way of
like yeah, like micro session, micro
pull request. Basically, like how people
are building like open source
software.
And you need to reach the stable power
loop of your project. And then you
Yeah, just like small iteration. Push it
and then you you can deploy like five
times a day, but
you have five files, 10 files, 15 five
max updated every time. And then you are
also able to catch the error
with Sentry or whatever like and boom
boom boom. Yeah. I do the exact same
thing. I always merge one branch that I
just updated into main. I never do like
five branches merging into one and then
merging into main because if it fails,
which one was the problem?
Yeah. Okay, so you open your pull
request, you merge to one, you test it.
And then yeah, I need to do that more.
>> I finish it before I go to the second
one. Yeah. And I know some people told
me why do you even test it yourself
because AI is smarter
and it will save you a lot of time if if
just have AI test everything, but I
tried it.
Yeah. And me doing it in steps and
testing myself as well just as a final
part after all the AIs debugging each
other. Yeah.
Um
if I look at my total time, I'm faster
doing every branch checking myself than
fully trusting AI and then needing to
debug everything. Yeah.
Yeah, I know 100% like it. I I spent a
day of QAing like
5 days of work here like yeah yesterday.
Um
yeah. Yeah, and you get annoyed. Why
didn't you fix this? How stupid are you?
Yeah, it's
yeah, it's so it's a little bit like
it's basically a QA loop of like that's
not working. Okay, try that. Okay, no.
Basically, what what I was doing like 5
years ago, I just did it like in a day
and then it's but yeah, it took it took
the day. It took the day to debug
everything.
Um but yeah, at the end it's working and
yeah, it's just like the again, night
it's more like 90/10. Like the AI is
doing 90% of the job like the last 10%
or human bottleneck and that's a that's
a problem. But how do you have a model
that can
that knows what's the design that you
want to use? Like you know, I'd say when
like yeah, you need to just let it go
and
AI is doing all of the shots, but I
don't know
which kind of quality product you're
going to end up with. No, I don't think
it's a good good quality product. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm just having AI document
everything. Yeah.
Yeah. And and still that's that's the
most basic so
I now did a full setup for a new project
with AI
and
it took me like a lot of hours to get
everything planned. Yeah. And eventually
we switched the way that we were
planning several times. So, after
planning, it did this, it did this and I
said, "Yeah, I'm not happy. I want to do
this, this, and this before we proceed
to the next step."
So, after I think 3 or 4 hours, we were
done planning.
And that's a lot of time. So, the first
thing I did, I asked it to write down
a full prompt to explain AI next time
how I want to do the planning exactly in
this style. So, now on my second
project, I just put in the MD file. I
say, "Read this. This is how I want to
do the planning. Okay, do we start?" And
then it just starts interviewing me.
"What do we need? How do we do this?
What is the setup? What server are we
using?" etc.
Yeah, okay. So, you have skills to
prepare your project. And do you do that
with like a new code base or
uh
you to cover a project? No, no, this was
a new code base. So, it was perfect for
setting up the skill. I like that. I
like I like scaffolding projects. You
know?
And uh yeah, by the way, I did that with
the ship ship V0 stuff and Spencer. It's
It's works well.
Uh
wait.
>> All the best experience he has, he is in
ship [__] Yeah.
Uh okay. So, baf baf
I'm going to show it here. Bam. Because
uh yeah, like if if those part are still
like uh finally getting all together, uh
that's that's lit. That's lit.
And on GitHub.
>> [laughter]
>> Back to the source, right? Yeah. Uh
okay. I want that.
I want that. Cool.
I'm like
up
back to GitHub.
Uh
back back.
back
up.
Okay. I want to get rid of the sidebar.
What the [__]
Okay, ship code.
Uh wait. Oh, no, I want that layout.
That will be better.
Oh, am I here?
Why is that not moving?
Hello? Yeah, we see the entire screen
now.
Oh.
[__]
Up.
And he's gone.
I
You left.
Yeah, that's possible. Okay. So, what
the heck?
Okay, I'm going to kill that. Uh
Cover, no.
Why?
Remove.
Good.
Uh share screen
window and screen.
Let's go back.
Back. Wow.
Uh chat
Hey, what's the plan? Oh, okay. Uh just
refresh. Oh, that's that's the plan.
Uh cool. So, yeah, ship ship got Nope, I
don't want that. I want
repository
uh V0 V0, yeah.
So, that's the a scaffold. Did you use
it?
Not yet. Okay. Uh so, it create like a
Basically, it's scaffolding an app like
um
uh
paperclip. Mhm.
And uh you can have like a API docs, uh
web landing page. Um
Electron uh so, desktop app, mobile app,
everything is in there. And uh it's it's
cool. And you just need to do uh NPX uh
ship ship dev V0, and then boom, you can
scaffold the project, and boom, and
that's it. It takes over your computer,
and it just fixes everything.
Exactly.
And uh yeah, it's
late. Oh, wait. I have the
V0. Bam. Yeah. Wow. Wow, the Claude GPT
Claude Claude website. Let's go.
Why is it to copy here? Like I could
have changed that.
Uh but yeah, just one command and then
boom, you have one website. Why am I
talking about that?
Because it's good. Yes, but I don't
remember what was the
>> [laughter]
>> Uh yeah, I don't I don't remember. We
were just talking about the best thing
you ever made. Oh, uh
oh, that's the thing that that's the
project I'm going to start tomorrow, you
know. Yeah, yeah.
But yeah, with the yeah, V0 like yeah,
scaffold that and then I was able to do
a demo, but yeah, that's not why I
wanted to talk about it. What what was
the question before?
I don't know. I can we have to scroll
back. Yeah.
Okay, so as a watcher, if you want to
know what we are talking about, just go
back.
>> [laughter]
>> Just scroll back and let us know so we
can proceed.
Um okay, so
yeah, okay. So I think we can
wrap it up here, but yeah, whatever. Uh
do you think do you think like software
that got rewritten by Before the AI wave
will be rewritten anyway because like to
identify and fix issues, right? Because
okay, AI is getting smarter, AI can
detect major issues.
Should we refactor internet?
Yes.
We should. We shouldn't prove it.
Yeah, let's let's rewrite WordPress,
too. Okay, so this weekend we need to
rewrite Salesforce,
Shopify because it's a stock
>> Because we can. Yeah. And he made
billions of profit. We want that as
well. Slash code like copy paste Shopify
boom boom boom. Yeah.
And tell me how to scale it. Yeah. And
make yeah, again, make no mistake
because I don't want security issues.
Yeah, exactly.
I I I think we are so far from that.
Like slash gold slash GitHub make me
GitHub open school. I don't think it's
even possible.
Because
it it needs to do such a big planning.
Yeah.
And you will need indefinite keys. Yeah.
Sorry,
tokens. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Oh, oh, oh, instead
like rebuilding Salesforce
you you create 1,000 software instead of
one big.
Yeah, that's better. You know, and like
yeah, it's I kind of like believe in in
the like one person software business
model.
You find a trend, you found a need, you
generated, and then let's go. Yeah, but
it's also easier to do. And it's fully
custom modeled for that person, so it
always works. You can load it on a
smaller server, no need to scale, no
need for load balancers, or whatever.
Yeah.
Exactly. Yeah, yeah, yeah, like even
like yeah, because of AI I really
install apps on my computer. Like
33.code I use the I use the the desktop
app. So, Kiyo saw all of those side
apps.
Uh I use them, and
there is a trend because as developer
you
you use the CLI on your computer, right?
Mhm. [clears throat] So, you want to
have access to that, or even to your own
computer to manage your files, etc., and
your emails, whatever, whatever that
could be on your computer by a client,
whatever.
Um or even like Adobe Premiere, like I
want to use Adobe Premiere via MCP, so
then I need access to my computer, etc.
Uh I even open clue, but bro, like the
whole open clue mania was because okay,
open clue can
take control of my computer.
Um
And if the software is rethinking is
completely rethink like that, that would
be that would be fun. Yeah, but don't
you think eventually it will just be AI?
It will just be cloud over
15.5 that
you just tell it to design something and
it says, "Okay, I did it. What file do
you want? Do you want a Figma file,
Photoshop file, InDesign file?" Good
luck. Yeah, yeah, but how cloud will end
on my uh Git project management
software?
Am I going to have my own GitHub, like
my own GitLab?
In a cloud instance and then it say,
"Oh, yeah. Oh, by the way."
Yeah, I just leaked it to everybody
else. Yeah, and basically also also I
deleted it. Yeah.
>> Cuz I run the migration. But the only
thing you need is database.
Yeah. And you connect it like an MCP
server and
it just pushes everything to your
database and connects it. That's it. Hm.
Yeah.
Okay.
So GitHub still have some hope to
stay relevant. They need to scale up
>> [laughter]
>> and need to perform better. Yeah, that's
sad. Okay, so should we conclude? Yes.
Tell us, what are you going to do? Uh
almost
>> [laughter]
>> like
Um
are we going to rewrite GitHub with
Codex?
Hm.
Maybe not. [laughter]
Maybe not.
And that's it. Bye.
Thank you for watching.
Uh yeah, like I
I I don't I
Hm.
Do I think we I I
I don't know. Like are we going to see
all of the big companies rewrite that
software that tech stack to
um at the agent age? I don't know.
Right. Yeah, and
do they even need to rewrite it? I I
think they will just keep on building
new functionality, and if you just keep
on scaling that part,
it will just replace it instead of
rebuilding it. Yeah.
Okay, and improve it. So, yeah, don't
don't If it's not broken, don't fix it,
and don't replace by AI code.
Yeah. And just keep on building for the
next part. Let's go.
Cool. Okay, thank you everyone for
watching this video. Thank you for
watching the live stream, and yeah,
we'll see you next week. And watch the
watch the subscribe button. Subscribe,
and watch the reels, watch the short. We
are on TikTok, Instagram, whatever. And
yeah, we have No, not whatever,
everywhere. Everywhere. And that's it.
Yes. Thanks for your time. Thanks you
for your time. I love the chat the
chit-chat, even if like a completely
brain shotgun.
>> [laughter]
>> Thank you, and enjoy your week. Thanks,
bro.